So this is a good time for a quick recap of the last couple of lessons.
现在快速总结下上几节课的内容
Here we have two models.
这是两个模型
The bad model in the left,
左侧是坏模型
and the good model in the right.
右侧是好模型
And for each one of those we calculate the cross entropy which is of sum of
我们算出每个模型的交叉熵
the negatives of the logarithms of the probabilities of the points being their colors.
即点是本身颜色的概率对数负值之和
And we conclude that the one on the right is better
并得出结论：右侧的模型更好
because a cross entropy is much smaller.
因为交叉熵更小
So let's actually calculate the formula for the error function.
我们计算下误差方程公式
Let's split into two cases.
拆分为两种情形
The first case being when y equals 1.
第一种是 y = 1
So when the point is blue to begin with,
首先是点是蓝色的情形
the model tells us that the probability of being blue is the prediction y_hat.
模型告诉我们蓝色的概率是预测 ŷ
So for these two points the probabilities are 0.6 and 0.2.
对于这两个点 概率是 0.6 和 0.2
As we can see, the point in the blue area has
可以看出 蓝色区域的点是蓝色的概率
more probability of being blue than the point in the red area.
比红色区域的点概率要高
And our error is simply the negative logarithm of this probability.
我们的误差是该概率的对数负值
So it's precisely minus logarithm of y_hat.
也就是 -ln(ŷ)
In the figure, it's minus logarithm of 0.6,
在图中是 -ln(0.6)
and minus logarithm of 0.2.
和 -ln(0.2)
Now, if y equals zero,
如果 y = 0
so when the point is red,
即点是红色
then we need to calculate the probability of the point being red.
那么我们需要计算点是红色的概率
The probability of the point being red is
点是红色的概率是
one minus the probability of the point being blue,
1 减去点是蓝色的概率
which is precisely 1 minus the prediction y_hat.
即 1-ŷ
So the error is precisely the negative logarithm of
所以误差是该概率对数的负值
this probability which is negative logarithm of 1 minus y_hat.
即 -ln(1-ŷ)
In this case, we get negative logarithm of 0.1,
这里是 -ln(0.1)
and negative logarithm of 0.7.
和 -ln(0.7)
So we conclude that the error is negative logarithm of y_hat and the point is blue.
我们得出结论：如果点是蓝色 则误差是 -ln(ŷ)
And negative logarithm of one minus y_hat if the point is red.
如果点是红色 则误差是 -ln(1-ŷ)
We can summarize these two formulas into this one.
我们可以将这两个公式总结为一个
Error equals negative one minus y logarithm of
Error = -(1-y)(ln(1-ŷ))-yln(ŷ)
Why does this formula work?
该公式为何可行？
Well, because if the point is blue,
因为如果点是蓝色
then y equals one which means one minus y equals zero which makes the first term zero.
那么 y = 1 则 1-y=0 使第一项变成 0
And the second term is simply logarithm of y_hat.
第二项就是 ln(ŷ)
Similarly, the point is red then y equals to zero.
类似地 如果点是红色 则 y=0
So the second term of the formula is 0,
公式的第二项变成 0
and the first one is logarithm of one minus y_hat.
第一项是 ln(1-ŷ)
Now, the formula for the error function is simply
现在误差函数的公式变成
the sum over all the error functions of the points.
所有点的误差函数之和
Which is precisely the summation here.
即这里的和
That's going to be this 4.8 we have here.
将是这里的 4.8
Now by convention, we'll actually consider the average not
按照惯例 我们将考虑平均值
the sum which is already dividing by m over here.
而不是和 它已经在这里除以 m
This will turn the 4.8 into a 1.2.
这样使 4.8 变成 1.2
From now on, we'll use this formula as our error function.
接下来我们将使用这个公式作为误差函数
Now, since y_hat is given by the sigmoid of the linear function Wx plus B,
因为 ŷ 是线性方程 Wx + b 的 s 型函数
then the total formula for the error is actually in terms
那么误差的总公式涉及的是
of W and B which are the weights of the model.
W 和 b 即模型的权重
And it's simply the summation we see here.
也就是这里的和
In this case, while i is just the label of the point X_i.
这里 i 是点 x(i) 的下角标
So now that we've calculated it,
我们已经得出公式
our goal is to minimize it.
现在的目标是简化它
And that's what we'll do next.
这将是接下来的任务
And just some small aside.
顺便提醒下
What we did is for binary classification problems.
我们针对的是二元分类问题
If we have a multiclass classification problem,
如果是有多个类别的分类问题
then the error is now given by the multiclass entropy.
那么误差将是多类别交叉熵
This formula is given here where for every data point we take the product of
这里的公式针对的是每个数据点
the labeled times the logarithm of the prediction and then we average all these values.
我们将标记类别的积乘以预测对数 然后对所有这些值求平均值
And again, it's a nice exercise to convince yourself that
同样可以自己计算验证下 当只有两个类别时
the two are the same when there are just two classes.
这两个公式实际上是一样的